She didn't come back to Earth alone.
The Astronaut is a science fiction, horror,
thriller film directed by Jess Varley.
After returning from her first space mission, astronaut Sam Walker is placed under
NASA’s care at a high security house for rehabilitation and medical testing.
However, when disturbing occurrences begin happening around the property, she
fears that something extraterrestrial has followed her back to Earth
Sam Walker, played by Kate Mara.
General William Harris, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Mark, played by Gabriel Luna.
Dr. Michelle Aiden, played by Ivana Miličević.
Izzy, played by Scarlett Holmes.
Val, played by Macy Gray.
The Astronaut is a 2025 American science fiction horror film written and directed by Jess Varley
and starring Kate Mara, Laurence Fishburne, Gabriel Luna, and  Ivana Miličević.
The film depicts an astronaut who believes an
extraterrestrial entity has followed her back to Earth.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of nasa, survival,
astronaut, surveillance, survival horror.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.